DANIFI KAPPER

WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT



danielkapper.com



dkapper01@gmail.com



github.com/dkapper01



314 226-7386



1884 Columbia Rd NW #905 Washington D.C.

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap

SASS

JQuery

JavaScript

React

Git

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A passionate and self-motivated learner that is dedicated to continuously expanding my skill set and experience as a Web Developer. Skilled and detail oriented coder with the ability to effectively communicate ideas, problems, and solutions individually or in collaboration with a team. Strategic thinker who is dedicated to continuous learning.

KEY PROJECTS

- Built a website that contains an algorithm written in JavaScript. The
 algorithm takes in a ransom note string and another magazines string
 to determine if the magazine contains all the letters from the note.
- Designed a dynamic, browser compatible dice game using HTML and CSS which integrated multiplayer functionality by manipulating the DOM with JavaScript and jQuery.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Titan House - Consultant

Washington, DC

November 2017 to Present

- Thoroughly research private equality firms portfolio companies.
- Build detailed profiles of chief executive officers working companies.
- Effectively manage my own productivity and produced quality.

Winco Windows, Inc. - Manager May 2015 to August 2017 St. Louis, MO

- Managed a team of five employees responsible for meeting daily and weekly deadlines by building a solid and helpful team environment.
- Trained and evaluated employee performance.
- Maintained inventory records and placed orders for new materials.

MedModo App - Co-founder January 2017 to June 2017 St. Louis, MO

- Designed a customer development program that measured how much value the app created for users.
- Acquired evidence to assist with deciding whether to pivot or proceed.
- Functioned as an enthusiastic member of the team in a fast-paced environment.
- Communicated daily updates to team members in scrum meetings.

EDUCATION

Missouri State University - Computer Science 2008 - 2011

Successfully completed 90 credits, including 27 Computer Science credits. GPA 3.4. Withdrew in good standing for financial reasons.

